

CONTACT

- +212652497590
- saidmia.dev@gmail.com
- linkedin.com/in/saidmia
- github.com/SaidM96

SKILLS

- Frontend Development
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript
- TailwindCSS, React, Next JS
- Redux, Tanstack-Query
- KYC
- Agil Methodologies: Linear, Jira
- Work with Figma, Zeplin
- Fast learning and Problem-Solving

EDUCATION

BACHELOR MATHEMATICS

University Ibn Zohr 2014 - 2018

ARCHITECT IN DIGITAL TECHNOLOGIES

1337 Coding school 2021

SAID MIA FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I am a dedicated Frontend Engineer specializing in ReactJS, Next.js, Tailwind CSS, TanStack Query, and Redux. With a strong passion for web development, I am constantly expanding my skill set and currently delving into the world of Web3. My experience allows me to create dynamic, responsive, and efficient web applications that meet modern standards.

EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND ENGINEER

at LendStack

Nov 2023 - Jul 2024 · 9 months · Full-time

- Work with nextjs, tailwind, react query and typescript to build a
 micro-finance website where users can manage their applications
 or create new one and go through steps to take a loan.
- Integrate chat with AI (GPT4) into our website
- add multi languages to the website (react-Internationalization)
- Integrate regula (KYC provider) into our website
- Integrate DAMAN-SIGN (e-signature provider)
- Agile methodologies, utilizing tools like Jira to manage projects and ensure continuous improvement.

FRONTEND ENGINEER

ACTIVIA CHALLENGE 2024

FEB 2024 - Apr 2024 · 9 months · Full-time

- Worked with nextjs, tailwind and react-query and typescript to build the website.
- the website had 100,000 visitors.